dubsado.com 2019-04-19

# Dubsado | Privacy

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally identifiable information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website. 

‍

### Dubsado and Privacy Shield

Dubsado is [self certified with Privacy Shield Certification](https://docs.wixstatic.com/ugd/862374_8eff4c844bd942efa66345429bf52cae.pdf). Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union to the United States. Dubsado has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>

‍

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, Dubsado commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. EU individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact Dubsado at: hello@dubsado.com.

‍

Dubsado has committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the Privacy Shield to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, established by JAMS. If Dubsado cannot address your complaint in a timely or sufficient manner, please contact them for more information and to file a complaint: <https://www.jamsadr.com/file-an-eu-us-privacy-shield-or-safe-harbor-claim>

Dubsado commits to cooperate with EU data protection authorities (DPAs) and comply with the advice given by such authorities with regard to human resources data transferred from the EU in the context of the employment relationship.

With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield Frameworks, Dubsado is subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. To learn more about the Privacy Shield Frameworks, visit the U.S. Department of Commerce’s [Privacy Shield website](https://www.privacyshield.gov/welcome). If there is any conflict between the Privacy Shield principles and this Policy, the principles will govern. Under certain conditions, Dubsado recognizes the rights of the individual to invoke binding arbitration. Dubsado may be liable in cases of onward transfers to third parties. 

You can read more details regarding Dubsado and Privacy Shield at our Privacy Shield Notice, [here.](https://www.dubsado.com/s/Dubsado-Final-Privacy-Shield-Notice.pdf)

‍

### 1\. What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app? 

Dubsado provides services that allow customers to manage various aspects of their businesses online. This includes client management, client relation and workflow automation services. In order to provide these services, we may be required to collect basic identification information including your name, company name, address, phone number and email address when registering for a new account. When registering, or when purchasing products in our store, we may also be required to collect financial information. This may include billing name, address and relevant billing info. 

Dubsado collects information via cookies and Web beacons (“Website Navigational Information”). Website Navigational Information includes standard information from your Web browser (such as browser type and browser language), your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, and the actions you take on the Company’s Websites (such as the Web pages viewed and the links clicked). 

We may also request information necessary to complete via client import or form building services and features. This could include the name, company name, address, phone number or email address of contacts that you disclose. All information provided for the sake of account building, be that important contacts or building forms is used strictly for the purposes you have instructed. Dubsado may also process your data when you attend or engage with our events or communities, online and in person. This would include basic contact information such as name for event purposes, or information you have instructed we may collect, like when interacting with an poll in our online communities. 

‍

### 2\. When do we collect information?

We may collect information from you when you interact with us regarding service or technical inquiries, register or engage on our webpages, engage with our social media, subscribe to a newsletter, participate in our in person and online communities, opt in to various account build services or enter information on our site, or interact with our various sub-processors and affiliates, listed below. 

‍

### 3\. How we use your information. 

Dubsado may use your information when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, browse the website, or use certain site features. This information allows us to fulfill user needs and requests, update our service and website, provide relevant value via promotions, surveys or other marketing/advertising, process transactions and for email content. Dubsado uses credit card/billing information only for the purpose of collecting payment from existing customers for services.

Cookies

Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process your log in information. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

​

We use cookies to help understand and save user’s preferences for future visits, and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf. 

​

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser’s Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

​

If users disable cookies in their browser:

​

You may disable cookies at any time. If you disable cookies, some features will be disabled. It will turn off some of the features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services may not function properly. 

​

Web Beacons

Dubsado utilizes Web Beacons in order to collect information about how users and prospective clients interact with company websites and emails. Web Beacons recognize various information about the cookies you have active or other information tied to when you interact with our content, allowing us to know how you are engaging with that content. The purpose of these web beacons is to help us provide a better web site, email and service experience.

​

IP Addresses and Log Files

Dubsado may also automatically collect information when you access our services. This may include Internet Protocol (“IP”) addresses, log files, pages viewed, browser type, links you interact with and other usage information. For example, we collect IP addresses to track and aggregate non-personal information, such as using IP addresses to allow us to identify the regions from which users navigate to our Services.  Dubsado may also collect IP addresses from users when they log into the Services as part of our log-in and security features.  

Third-party disclosure and Third-party link.

​

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties no listed in this privacy policy, your personally identifiable information. 

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

​

Google

Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. <https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en>

​

We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website. 

​

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy. 

​

We have implemented the following: Demographics and Interests Reporting 

​

We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website. 

​

Opting out:   
Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

​

Social Media

Dubsado utilizes social media in it’s marketing and advertising. When you interact with Dubsado related social media content, for example, “liking” content on our Facebook page, such interaction may allow us to collect your IP address or the page you are visiting from. Cookies may also be enables to allow various features to function properly. Interactions on social media are subject to the privacy policy of the social media service provider. 

‍

### 4\. How we share information

Sub-Processors

Dubsado is responsible for the processing and handling of personal data it receives under the Privacy Shield Framework, including the onward transfer liability provisions. 

In order to allow services on our behalf, Dubsado may share data about visitors and customers with our contracted service providers. Service providers are only authorized to use personal information necessary to complete the services requested. Dubsado may also share Data about Dubsado Visitors, Customers and Huddle Attendees with the Company’s service providers or partners to ensure information quality, and with third–party social networking and media Web sites, for marketing and advertising on said sites. Unless described in this Privacy Statement, Dubsado does not share, sell, rent, or trade any information with third parties for their promotional purposes. 

Our contracted service providers which provide services such as IT and system administration and hosting, credit card processing, research and analytics, marketing, customer support and data enrichment; such service providers comprise companies located in the countries in which we operate. 

Dubsado uses the following Sub Processors:

  * Amazon Web Services, Inc.

  * Intercom R&D Unlimited Company

  * Intuit, Inc.

  * Square, Inc.

  * Stripe, Inc. 

  * PayPal (Europe) S.á.r.l. et Cie, S.C.A. d/b/a Braintree

  * The Rocket Science Group LLC d/b/a MailChimp

  * Cloudspot, Inc.

  * Zapier, Inc. 

  * Cronofy Limited

  * Cloudinary Ltd

  * Google LLC  

Partners and Affiliates

Dubsado maintains various partner and affiliate relationships in order to offer joint products, services, offers, and functionality. If you choose to opt into integration or use of these joint offerings through Dubsado or our partners/affiliates, Dubsado may share or collect information regarding your interest of said offerings or services. Dubsado may be liable in cases of onward transfers to third parties. If you do not want your information shared with Dubsado partners and affiliates, you may chose to not opt into their specific integrations, services, offers or any other interaction.  

​

Events and Collaborations

When you attend in person or online events hosted by Dubsado (webinars, The Huddle, etc) or participate in a giveaway, contest or promotion for which Dubsado is sponsoring, we may collect and share your information. Examples include if you submit your name and contact for collection in order to win a prize, or to receive an invite to a meetup. When you do this, your information will be subject to the privacy statements of all parties involved. 

​

Billing Information

Dubsado uses third-parties in regards to payment processing. These payment processors may not use your personal information for any reason outside processing your credit card information for the intended services. 

Compelled Disclosure

Dubsado may be required to disclose personal information in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. 

‍

### 5\. Communication Subscription Settings

Dubsado allows you to to “unsubscribe” from email communications, via a link at the bottom of all company related emails. You may also unsubscribe by contacting us at [hello@dubsado.com](mailto:hello@dubsado.com) at any time. 

CAN SPAM Act

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations. 

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at: [hello@dubsado.com](mailto:hello@dubsado.com)  and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.

‍

### 6\. Security

Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible. We do not use Malware Scanning.

​

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

​

We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information. All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.  Any person with a link to a document you send to a client can be accessed.  Do not use documents to share or store credit card information, passwords, or other personal sensitive information. 

​

An in-depth look at our Data Protection Policies, your rights as a customer, as well as Data Protection Addendum can be found [here](https://static1.squarespace.com/static/57851f0af7e0abff17796539/t/5afdf08a352f53ba55e6ce39/1526591627569/Completed+Dubsado+Data+Processing+Addendum++%282%29+%282%29.pdf), per GDPR regulations. 

​

California Online Privacy Protection Act

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law’s reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. – See more at: <http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf>

Users can visit our site anonymously. Our Privacy policy is linked on our home page or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website. Our Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’ and can be easily be found on the page specified above. 

Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes: On our Privacy Policy Page Users are able to change their personal information: by emailing us, by logging in to their account or by chatting with us or sending us a ticket. 

​

How does our site handle do not track signals?

We don’t honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place. We don’t honor them because our system relies on cookies. 

Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?

It’s also important to note that we do not allow third-party behavioral tracking. 

​

COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation’s consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under 13.

​

Fair Information Practices

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information. 

In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices as well as GDPR regulations we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur, we will notify the users via email within 7 business days. 

​

We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle and GDPR, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors. 

‍

### 7\. Duration of Processing

Dubsado reserves the right to maintain your information for the length of time necessary to carry out intended services. This allows us to perform all necessary business operations, or meet any legal obligations. When you close your account, we may continue to communicate with you about our Services, give you important business updates that may affect you, and let you know about products and services that may interest you, unless you have opted out of receiving marketing communications. 

‍

### 8\. Data Correction, Access and Retention

At any time, you reserve the right to access, rectification, erasure, restriction of processing, data portability, object and to not be subject to automated decision making regarding data you have submitted. EU individuals and Swiss individuals have certain rights to access Personal Information about them, and to limit use and disclosure of their Personal Information. Dubsado has committed to respect those rights. Dubsado account holders are able to update general information and billing information by accessing their brand settings. In order to terminate your subscription, you must do so through your Dubsado dashboard. In order to exercise these rights, or to request the return, review or deletion of Data,  please contact [hello@dubasdo.com](mailto:hello@dubasdo.com). All requests will be managed within a reasonable amount of time. 

​

Contacting Us  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us and our Data Protection Officer using the information below.

​

100 East Tujunga Avenue #201  
Burbank, California 91502

United States

Last Edited on 2018-04-02

‍
